{
    "id": "6e4aef3d11a1489386289e85b68fc331",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was amazed ……………………….. their brilliant performance.",
            "description": "Amaze is followed by the preposition at.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is afflicted ………………………. leprosy.",
            "description": "Afflict is followed by with.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Alcohol does not agree ………………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize ………………………… your bad behavior.",
            "description": "We write for after apologize.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She often boasts ………………………….. her success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "One must not brood ………………………. one’s failures.",
            "description": "Brood is followed by over.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We called …………………………… them yesterday.",
            "description": "To call on is to visit.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been charged …………………………… treason.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not want to compete …………………….. anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The merchant deals …………………………. precious metals.",
            "description": "Deal in can mean sell.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "One must not deviate …………………………. the path of truth and virtue.",
            "description": "Deviate is followed by from.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has never shown any interest …………………….. politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}